letgame.net 2013-09-17

# Privacy Policy | LetGame.net

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Information That is Publicly Available**

  * When you create a YouTube Account, some information about your YouTube Account, your videos and your account activity will be provided to other users of YouTube and sites embeded these videos same as letgame.net. 
  * Your YouTube Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on YouTube, such as when you upload videos or send messages through YouTube. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site. 
  * Any videos that you submit to YouTube may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other YouTube users or other websites embeded them(Ex: letgame.net). 
  * You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your YouTube Account channel page. If you choose to add certain features to your YouTube Account channel page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other users and may be aggregated and shared with your friends or other users. Such shared activity may include your favorite videos, videos you rated and videos that you have uploaded. 
  * Youtube support webmasters with APIs to view without having to go to YouTube sites.You can view this information here: [youtube on your site](http://www.youtube.com/youtubeonyoursite).And letgame.net collected these videos from Youtube, we did not host or upload any videos, films, media files.Thus, letgame.net is absolutly legal.However, If you do not want to showing your videos on other sites, please log into youtube.com and disable the option to have the videos be embeddable on external websites. 

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Cpmstar, Adtoll, Adengage,.... Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact me by email to: Contact us
